[Music]
in this release wave we're making it
easier to get crucial information into
business Central and intelligent
insights out let's check it out first we
know that when business is doing well
it's really easy to spend lots of time
capturing content in business Central
new customers new sales opportunities
and so on autofill is here to make that
a lot easier say your team member comes
in and creates a new customer account
they add the name and click suggest and
the autofill magic happens autofill uses
a number of different ways to suggest
the likely answer it can search the web
to look up the address of the customer
it could suggest the most frequently
used or most sensible answer for the
next field and so on autofill is a huge
productivity booster and Time Saver
using the power of AI grounded in
business Central data when your business
Central environment is full of Rich data
you want to be able to consume it
quickly with a new summarized capability
you can do just that on the most used
pages in business Central you can now
see an instant summary presented by
copilot why is this summary so helpful
it's not just servicing what's important
or urgently needs your attention from
that page but also from related Pages
including information from Custom Fields
providing you with really impactful
insights that are tailored to your role
the quick links will direct you straight
to where that content is in in the
record so that you can go from insight
to making decisions and taking action in
record timing need more information
simply click to get more insights and
ask co-pilot how to take action finally
it's more important than ever to be able
to understand and report on the
sustainability of your processes on new
scope 3 value chain process automation
is now embedded across the standard
business Central Erp processes the
feature will automatically calculate the
carbon dioxide equivalent for your
finished goods by using raw material
emissions data from purchase documents
and adding emissions from operations in
manufacturing processes providing you
with the figures you need to report on
your indirect emissions data across your
upstream and downstream value chain
scope 3 represents the majority of your
emissions and is the most complex to
measure so we're excited to give you the
capabilities to more easily calculate it
information that we know influences your
business decisions and aligns with many
regulations there's so much more coming
please to the release wave notes to
learn more
[Music]